The first black woman president of Harvard has been asked to step down amidst questions over
plagiarism. Now, let me just tell y'all, this sister was there at the committee. They were
asking her questions about how they're handling antisemitism at Harvard. And in my opinion,
I feel like she was toeing the line, but this is what happens. We get these positions at these
institutions and we'd be the first in that position at the institution. And now we feel
compelled to have to show up a certain way to make way for more of us to be in there. But
oftentimes that way that we have to show up includes us having to toe the line, includes
respectability, politics, et cetera, et cetera. And now, even though she did all of that, you know
what, we going to sift around and find something to smear her with so that she got to head on out.
Damn shame. And she now has the shortest tenure of a person in this position.
Tenure, shorter than a haircut.